

# Loan Tran Duy

FRONT-END DEVELOPER

UX / UI DESIGNER

GRAPHIC DESIGNER

loantranduy.com

+61 434 979 909 tdl.tranduy@gmail.com Bronte NSW, Australia

[ Working Holiday Visa ]

# Languages

French Native

English Intermediate

Spanish Beginner

Dutch Beginner

Versatile 25 years old Belgian Creative Developer with 4+ years of experience being the bridge communication gap between designers & developers. Specializes in React and styled components. Well-versed in Scrum and Agile. Learning is what really drives me, that's why I love to share & learn from my teammates.

#### Front-end

HTML React ♥

CSS / SCSS JavaScript

Bootstrap / CSS Grid jQuery

Styled Components ♥ Handlebars

#### CMS

Wordpress BigCommerce
Joomla Custom CMS

#### **Team Tools**

Git FreedCamp / Trello
Slack Zeplin

# Web Design

UX Icons Illustration
UI Advanced Prototyping

#### Tools

Sketch App ♥ InVision

Principle Adobe Illustrator

GlooMap Zeplin

## **Graphic Design**

Adobe After Effects

Brand Identity Packaging

Stationery Design Motion Graphic ♥

Illustration Video Editing

#### Tools

Adobe Illustrator Adobe Premier Pro
Adobe Photoshop Adobe Lightroom
Adobe In Design Pencil & Paper ♥

# Education

MAR 2018 - 5 DAYS

#### Advanced React intensive Masterclass

Hackages Masterclass | Brussels

OCT 2017 - 5 DAYS

#### React intensive Masterclass

Hackages Masterclass | Brussels

OCT 2017 - 2 DAYS

#### **Advanced Javascript MasterClass**

Hackages Masterclass | Brussels

JANV 2017 - SEP 2017

#### Certificate Front-end Developer

CEPEGRA | Charleroi

MAY 2016 - JANV 2017

# Certificate Web Interface Designer

CEPEGRA | Charleroi

SEP 2013 - JUN 2016

# Bachelor Graphic & Advertising Communication

HEAJ | Namur

+61 434 979 909 tdl.tranduy@gmail.com Bronte NSW, Australia

[ Working Holiday Visa ]



### Experience

MAY 2018 - PRESENT

#### Freelance Designer & Developer

TRAN DUY LOAN Sprl

In 2018, I took the decision to create my own company and start working as freelancer in frontend development, web design & graphic design.

Take a look to my portfolio loantranduy.com.

MAY 2018 - MAY 2019

#### Freelance Front-end Developer

Van de Velde | Gent, Belgium

Working closely with designers, implementing pixel perfect web designs. The challenge was to develope one template aimed at three different Van de Velde-owned brands. "Marie Jo", "Primadonna" & "Andres Sarda".

OCT 2017 - MAY 2018

#### Interactive Designer

Hackages | Brussels, Belgium

I was responsible at all creation steps of the platform. Brainstorming, wireframing, designing & developing new innovative features and proof of concepts according to project requirements.

SEP 2017

#### Intern Interactive Designer

Hackages | Brussels, Belgium

Working in pair with the lead designer to improve the current design of their website and their whole brand identity. Business cards, stationery design, powerpoint, ...

MAR 2017 - APRIL 2017

#### Intern UX / UI Designer

Arkam | Mons, Belgium

Logo creation, brand identity, CMS customization for a wide variety of clients

JANV 2016 - MAR 2016

#### Intern Graphic / Web Designer

Elle Belgium Magazine | Lasne, Belgium

Designing leaderboards, banners, social media content and editing the magazine layout.